RG 169:007, Connecticut Forest and Park Association
Connecticut State Library
- Series 6. Committee Files, 1929-2011
  - Hiking Trails Committee, 1929-2011
    - Mattatuck Trail - Waterbury section, 1929-1944 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Metacomet Trail - New Britain section, 1930-1947 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Middletown section, 1931-1949 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Naugatuck Valley section, 1932-1949 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Nepaug Trail, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - New Haven section, 1929-1959 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - New Preston section, 1940-1944 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Newtown section, 1937-1943 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Norwich section, 1932-1957 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Old Lyme, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Peoples Forest, 1929-1942 (Box 12, Folder 17-19)
    - Permissions and easements, 1936-1971 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Quinnipiac Trail - Waterbury section, 1930-1957 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Roxbury section (Waramaug Trail), 1941-1948 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Shelton section, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Shenipsit and Gay City Trails, 1960-1965 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Shenipsit Trail, 1973-1977 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Shore line trails, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Stamford section, 1932-1946 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - State trails, 1941-1958 (Box 12, Folder 28-30)
    - Storrs section, 1931-1948 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Suffield section, 1933-1947 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Talks and publicity, 1930-1941 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Torrington section, 1937-1948 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Tunxis Trail, 1967-1979 (Box 12, Folder 35-36)
    - Walk Book, 3rd edition, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Wallingford section, 1937-1948 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Washington, Connecticut, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Westerly Rhode Island section, 1935-1948 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Willimantic, 1932-1949 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Winsted section, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Woodbridge section, 1932-1934 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Woodstock section, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Series 7. Reports and Studies, 1910-2010
  - A challenge for New England: changes in large forest land holdings, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Blue Blazed Hiking Trails report, 2002-2010 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Botany 411 - the freshwater wetlands of Bluff Point Coastal Reserve, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - The business of agriculture, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut ecoregion program, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Energy Advisory Board - report to the governor and general assembly, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Connecticut environment review, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut's farmland preservation program annual report, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association annual report, 1959-2002 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association annual report, 2004-2008 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association development reports, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association report of annual meeting, 1958-2003 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association report of annual meeting, 1984-2008 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association report of the president, 1935-1984 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association report of the secretary, 1932-1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association report of the secretary, 1953-1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association summary tables and charts, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut forest roundtable report - input from Connecticut forest stakeholders, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Connecticut General Statutes relating to forestry and forest fire control and federal laws relating to forestry, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Connecticut's vanishing landscape - the case for land conservation in Connecticut, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Connecticut watershed conservation network conference notes, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Department of Environmental Protection, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Development plan 2003-2010 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Draft strategic plan, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Driveway impact at Meriden Road, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Eastern Connecticut resource conservation and development area, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Environmental quality in Connecticut, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Forest health highlites - northeastern states, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Forest statistics for Connecticut - 1972 and 1985, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Forester annual report form, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Goodwin Forest Conservation Education Center annual report, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Guide to trip by New England section of American Foresters, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Guidelines for gypsy moth control recommended by Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Landowner attitudes and forest land use in northeastern Connecticut, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Memorandum 25: organization, powers and duties, personnel and expenditures of the Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Memorandum 30: organization, powers and duties, personnel and expenditures of the State Park and Forest Commission, 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Memorandum 34: organization, powers and duties, personnel and expenditures of the Commission on Forests and Wildlife, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Memorandum 41: adequacy of state recreational facilities, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Memorandum 43: state forests and state parks in Connecticut, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Memorandum 44: finances of state departments controlling recreational land, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Memorandum 44A: summary of state's interest in recreation, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Metacomet - Mattabesett - Monadnock Trail study - Connecticut GIS project, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Metacomet - Mattabesett - Monadnock Trail system - national scenic trail feasibility study and environmental assessment draft report, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Mystic River Watershed greenway plan, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Natural resources task force, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - 1972 Department of Environmental Protection investigation, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Non point source pollution: an assessment and management plan, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Notable trees, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Opportunities and limitations of our resources and the state of our state in 2000 A.D., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Planning for sea level rise in southern New England, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Proposal for a New England Natural Resources Center, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Quinebaug - Shetucket Heritage Corridor, 2005 annual report (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Recreational uses of utility and transportation corridors in northeastern Connecticut, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Report of the civic improvement commission, 1910 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Report of the special committee on employment of a forester, undated (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Report of the special committee on finance, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Report of the forestry committee, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Response of the Department of Environmental Protection to draft report of Legislative Program Reviews and Investigations Committee, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Review of trail agreements, license agreements and easements, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Salmon Brook Associates, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - State of the State Parks, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Statement on the effects of pollution on our coastal and estuarine waters, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - SCORP - Connecticut outdoor recreation 1989 action plan (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Taxing the tree farm - sensible policies for sensible private forestry, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Vegetation - management of wetland forests, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Series 8. Publications, circa 1883-2011
  - Connecticut Department of Environmental Protection. Agriculture and Wetlands Protection in Connecticut, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - The Billboard: A Blot on Nature and a Parasite on Public Improvements. New York: Committee of State and Local Officials of New York and Civic Organizations, 1939 January 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Blue Blazes: A Newsletter for CFPA Volunteers. Middlefield, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1997-2011 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Graves, Arthur Harmount. "Breeding Chestnuts for Timber". Journal of the New York Botanical Garden 50, no. 599, 1949 November (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Newall, Charles A. Bridle Trails in Massachusetts, 1934 January 27 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Fernow, Bernard E. A Brief History of Forestry in Europe, The United States, and Other Countries: A course of lectures delivered before the Yale Forest School. New Haven: Price, Lee, & Adkins Co., 1907 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Graves, Arthur Harmount. The Brooklyn Botanical Garden, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Celebrate 75 Years - Connecticut State Parks, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Barrell, Joseph. Central Connecticut in the Geologic Past. Bulletin No. 23. Hartford: State of Connecticut State Geological and Natural History Survey, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Sweeney, Frank. The Changing Forest Situation A Study of Conservation on State and Private Forest Lands. New York: American Enterprise Association, Inc., 1950 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Gephard, Stephen R. A History of Chapman's Pond and its Preservation, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Hawes, Austin F. Chestnut in Connecticut and the Improvement of the Woodlot. Bulletin 154, Forestry Publication No. 2. New Haven: Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1906 September (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Connecticut, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Jenkins, Edward H. Connecticut Agriculture. Reprinted from History of Connecticut. State History Company, Inc., circa 1925 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station bulletin numbers 54, 174, 194, 201, 237, 262, 292, 328, 412, 413, 463, 494, 523, and 545, 1913-1951 (Box 14, Folder 23-25)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station reports, 1913, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - The Connecticut Council on Environmental Quality Annual Report, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Connecticut Forestry Association The Outlook in 1902 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Connecticut Forestry Association, 1923-1928 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Buttrick, P.L. Town Forests and Parks for Connecticut. Publication number 15. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association, 1925; 2 duplicate booklets
    - Roadside Shade Trees A Manual of Roadside Improvements for Tree Wardens and Others Interested. Publication number 18. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association, 1928; 2 duplicate manuals
    - Connecticut Forests. Connecticut Forestry Association publication number 12. New Haven: Yale University Press, 1923; 3 duplicate publications
    - A Forest, Park and Wild Life Conservation Program for Connecticut. Outline of Forestry and allied Legislation submitted to 1925 Session of Connecticut General Assembly. Connecticut Forestry Association publication number 14. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association
    - Buttrick, P.L. Highway Trees and Roadside Improvement for Connecticut. Connecticut Forestry Association publication number 16. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association, 1926
    - State Forests and Parks - A Dividend Paying Investment for Connecticut. Connecticut Forestry Association publication number 17. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association, 1927
  - Winslow, Mary. "Connecticut Forestry Association - A Bit of History". Connecticut Quarterly 4, no. 3, circa 1898; typescript copy (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Connecticut Forestry Association bulletins (Box 14, Folder 31-33)
    - Fourth Annual Bulletin of the Connecticut Forestry Association., 1906; 2 duplicate bulletins
    - Fifth Annual Bulletin of the Connecticut Forestry Association. Publication number 5. Hartford: The Hartford Printing Co., 1907; 2 duplicate bulletins
    - Proceedings of the Connecticut Forestry Association. Publication number 6. Hartford: The Hartford Printing Co., 1909; 2 duplicate bulletins
    - Proceedings of the Connecticut Forestry Association. Publication number 7. Hartford: The Hartford Printing Co., 1909-1911; 5 duplicate bulletins
    - Proceedings of the Connecticut Forestry Association. Publication number 8. Hartford: The Hartford Printing Co., 1912-1914; 4 duplicate bulletins
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association bulletins, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Connecticut Forestry Association publications, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 35-36)
    - A Forestry Policy for Connecticut. Report of a Special Meeting of the Connecticut Forestry Association held in Hartford, Connecticut, November 27, 1920. Publication number 9., 1921; 5 duplicate reports
    - Connecticut Forestry Association proceedings, 1922 September 1; 4 duplicate reports
    - Graves, H. S. What State Forests will Mean to Rural Connecticut. Reprinted from 1923 report of the Connecticut Forestry Association. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association, 1924
    - Greely, W. B. Use of Idle Land. Reprinted from 1923 report of the Connecticut Forestry Association. New Haven: Connecticut Forestry Association, 1924
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association News, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association Newsletter, 1968-1979 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Includes notices and programs for field meetings.
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association Newsletter, 1979-1988 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association pamphlets, circa 1934-2004 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - A little foresight...can protect our landscape - forever. The Hibbard Trust for Land and Trails, circa 2004
    - The Connecticut Forest and Park Association, undated
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association Conserving Connecticut's Land and Natural Resources Join Today, undated
    - Connecticut Forest Facts, undated; 2 pamphlets
    - Connecticut's Forest Stewardship Program, undated
    - Conserving Connecticut, undated; 2 pamphlets
    - Dollars from your Woodlot. Publication number 39, 1938
    - Motor Vehicles and Taxes in Connecticut, circa 1934; 4 duplicate pamphlets
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association publications, 1928-1965 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The People's Forest. What it is and How it Answers the Question: What can you do for Forestry in Connecticut? Publication number 13. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1924 March
    - The People's Forest. What it is and How it Answers the Question: What can you do for Forestry in Connecticut? 3rd edition. Publication number 13. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1928 April; 2 duplicate copies
    - Connecticut's State Forest Purchase Program. An Address of Herman H. Chapman, President of Commission on Forests and Wild Life. Delivered at the Annual Meeting of the Connecticut Forest and Park Association, Hartford, Connecticut, March 13, 1935. Publication number 27. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 7 duplicate publications
    - Connecticut Ski Trails. Publication number 34. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1937 January
    - Chapman, H. H. Shall Our State Parks be Self Supporting? Publication number 38. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1938 May
    - Heermance, Edgar L. Practical Forestry and Forest Trees of Connecticut. Publication number 40. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1939 May; 3 duplicate publications
    - How to Burn Wood: New Methods and New Markets. Fourth revised edition. Publication number 33c. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1941
    - Town Forests. Publication number 44. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1945 May
    - Forest Trees of Southern New England. Publication number 45b. East Hartford: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1965
  - The Connecticut Guide. Hartford: Emergency Relief Commission, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hicock, Henry W. and Bruce B. Miner. Connecticut in Perspective: A Bicentennial View of Its Land and Its People. Reprinted from Connecticut Woodlands Summer-Fall issue, 1976. East Hartford: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, circa 1976; 2 duplicate publications (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Sohon, Julian A. and Dr. Alexander N. Winchell, ed. Connecticut Minerals their Properties and Occurance. Bulletin number 77. Hartford: State of Connecticut State Geological and Natural History Survey, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut's Forest Fire Problem. Report on the State-Wide Forest Fire Conference held at Hartford, Connecticut, 1926 June 24 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Whyte, William H. Connecticut's Natural Resources A Proposal for Action, 1962 June (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Good, Peter, Julie Victoria and Jenny Dickson. Connecticut's Nonharvested Wildlife Program: A Summary of Current Projects and Activities. Hartford: Department of Environmental Protection, Bureau of Natural Resources, Wildlife Division, 1994 January (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "What Connecticut's Environmentalists Expect of You". Connecticut Nursery and Landscape issue 1, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - The Connecticut River Guide. Greenfield, MA: Connecticut River Watershed Council, Inc., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Guide envelope contains a book and 3 maps.
  - Connecticut State Parks, 1917, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut State Parks A Reprint of the Report of the State Park Commission to the Governor. Hartford: State of Connecticut, 1917
    - Connecticut State Parks A Report on their Growth, Cost, and Use, 1914-1931. Hartford: State Park and Forest Commission, 1932 October
  - The Connecticut Trail System "Follow the Blue Blazes" trail folders, 1928-1935 (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
    - Appalachian Trail. Publication number 19 M. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1934 May 10
    - Appalachian Trail. Publication number 19 N. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1934 May; 5 duplicate trail folders
    - Appalachian Trail, South Portion. Publication number 19 F. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1931 October; 2 duplicate trail folders
    - Mattabesett Trail. Publication number 19 K. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1932 May; 4 duplicate trail folders
    - Mattatuck Trail. Publication number 19 J. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1932 May; 5 duplicate trail folders
    - Mattatuck Trail. Publication number 19 Q. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1936 February; 2 copies
    - Mattatuck Trail, Eastern Section. Publication number 19-I. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1932 April 11
    - Metacomet Trail. Publication number 19 O. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1935 October; 2 duplicate trail folders
    - Quinnipiac Trail. Publication number 19 D. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1931 July; 5 duplicate trail folders
    - Quinnipiac Trail. Publication number 19 E. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1931 September; 4 duplicate trail folders
    - Quinnipiac Trail, Southern Portion. Publication number 19 A. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1930 April; 2 duplicate trail folders
    - Tunxis Trail, Southern Portion. Publication number 19 G. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1931 October
    - Tunxis Trail, Southern Portion. Publication number 19 G, second edition. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1932 November; 5 duplicate trail folders
    - Tunxis Trail, Southern Section. Publication number 19-L. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1932 May 28; 3 duplicate trail folders
    - Mattatuck Trail. Publication number 19 Q. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1936 February 7
    - Mattabesett Trail and Metacomet Trail, Southern Portion. Publication number 19 P. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1935 November 15; 2 duplicate trail folders
  - Connecticut outdoor recreation guides, 1936, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Outdoor Recreation Guide for State Parks and Forests in Connecticut. Publication number 31. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1936 May; 2 duplicate copies
    - Connecticut Outdoor Recreation Guide. Bicentennial edition. Publication number 46-A. East Hartford: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1976
  - Connecticut State College Extension Service bulletins, 1923-1948 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Moss, A. E. Growing Timber as a Farm Crop. Bulletin number 59. Storrs, CT: Connecticut Agricultural College Extension Service, 1923 February
    - Living from the Farm. Bulletin number 182. Storrs, CT: Connecticut State College Extension Service, 1933 April
    - Morgan, M. F. and Albert E. Wilkinson. Fertilizer and Lime for Vegetables. Bulletin number 265. Storrs, CT: Connecticut State College Extension Service, 1938 June
    - Rollins, H. A. Red Raspberry Culture in Connecticut. Bulletin number 275, revision of bulletin number 172. Storrs, CT: Connecticut State College Extension Service, 1939 March
    - Morgan, M. F. and H. G. M. Jacobson. Soil Management for Intensive Vegetable Production on Sandy Connecticut Valley Land. Bulletin number 439. New Haven: Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1940 October
    - Kienholz, Dr. Raymond and Floyd M. Callward Forest Weeding. Bulletin number 310. Storrs, CT: University of Connecticut Extension Service, 1941 June
    - Fenton, Richard H. and Floyd M. Callward. Home-Grown Christmas Trees for Connecticut. Bulletin number 409. Storrs, CT: Extension Service, College of Agriculture, University of Connecticut, 1933 April
  - 50th Anniversary Connecticut State Park & Forest Commission, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut State Parks Major Projects. For the Biennium ending June 30, 1937. Designs Specially Prepared for the Legislative Committees on State Parks and Reservations and on Appropriations, 1935 March 15; 3 copies (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut State Parks & Recreation Areas. Hartford: State of Connecticut Department of Environmental Protection, Office of State Parks and Recreation, undated; 1 pamphlet (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut State Parks A Report of their Growth, Cost, and Use 1914-1931. Hartford: State Park and Forest Commission, 1932 October (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - SCORP Connecticut Statewide Comprehensive Outdoor Recreation Plan 1987-1992. Fifth revision. Hartford: State of Connecticut Department of Environmental Protection, circa 1987 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut Walk Books, 1937-1984 (Box 15, Folder 18-27)
    - Connecticut Walk Book. Publication number 36. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1937 October
    - Connecticut Walk Book Revised Edition with Ski Trails. Publication number 36c. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1940 May; 2 duplicate walk books
    - Connecticut Walk Book Third Edition. Publication number 36d. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1946 August
    - Connecticut Walk Book Fourth Edition. Publication number 36e. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1953 September
    - Connecticut Walk Book Fifth Edition. Publication number 36g. Wallingford, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1961 July; 2 duplicate walk books
    - Connecticut Walk Book Sixth Edition. Publication number 36i. Hartford: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1965
    - Connecticut Walk Book Seventh Edition. Publication number 36j. Hartford: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1968
    - Connecticut Walk Book Ninth Edition. Publication number 36L. East Hartford, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1971